Soon she will be born.
He would be a powerful Orc.
You will have offspring.
It's all thanks to you.
You will have a friend for practice.
There will be no one
can stop our war group.
Our enemies will die.
She said what?
- He asked forgiveness for his son.
- Ignore him.
Magic of Gul'dan.
Fuel for my magic is life threatening.
You are the strongest warrior.
When we arrive, we will
take our enemies as fuel.
And we will bring
destruction to them all.
Let me go first.
You're carrying a baby
in my battle group?
Poor woman.
The new knight for Horde.
Come here, I have something for you.
- What is wrong?
- Miracle mechanic.
Read this.
Go home. Someone will come.
- We found something.
- Are you from there?
Healthy.
You are there?
What are you doing here?
- Let me finish this.
- No one can do that.
- What's that?
- Guardian.
Call the king and the Guardian.
What kind of wild thing to do that?
- Release him.
- Honourable.
- What is it, a witch?
- I want to be Guardian of the year.
Who wants to carry you?
I have an ability.
There are dark forces are very
close, we can not ignore it.
- Take him away.
- Good, sir.
Your Excellency, call the Guardian.
What is wrong?
- What?
- Maybe he's right.
- Dad will not believe.
- My son does not need your help.
I was the queen.
And also my sister.
How long since that time?
- 6 years?
- No contact at all.
- No need to start now.
- Guardian calling.
- All was subdued.
- Respect our honor.
Do not kill too many,
we need them alive.
- Lothar.
- Karos.
Many things have changed.
- Where is he?
- I did not know there was this many books.
Do not touch anything.
Glad to see you, Lothar.
Guardian need your help.
He could not resist you.
- You called him?
- No.
- What are you doing?
- I make sculptures.
It took a long time without magic.
- Have a drink.
- Thank you.
Glad to see you. I brought this.
Hello? Who are you?
- What are you doing?
- Guardian, do not.
I do not mean all sorts.
- Let me explain.
- Explain what?
I'm a researcher.
Many secret knowledge in this place.
The great strength that can
be catastrophic for Azeroth.
I'm doing the right thing.
- Honourable.
- It's been a long time.
During this time there
was never a problem.
- What is this?
- There is a team.
A monster that can not be stopped.
Many who have been affected.
- We have to get ready.
- We do not know anything about them.
We need information.
We must protect this government.
I was the Guardian, it is my duty.
- Yes you're right. Who is he?
- Sorry, Your Honor.
What do you think?
Starting from there.
Guardian.
Alert!
Guardian!
Do not be afraid of them.
You have to be smart.
- What are you doing?
- I have to go back.
Good luck.
- Where Guardian?
- He's back.
- Di mana kudamu
-? Mereka mengambil kudaku.
Hold it right there.
Do not come close.
I will kill him.
He scares me.
Right here!
Can you spell? As Guardian.
Creature are you? Why
did you attack our land?
- He does not understand a word you're saying.
- You can speak our language?
You got a name?
You understand our language.
Once again, you have a name?
Garona. Day menyebut
dirinya sendiri Garonne.
- What the hell are you?
- A wild creature.
- Orc.
- Orc? That's you?
I know all the races in the Seven
Kingdoms. I've never heard of orcs.
Show me where you come from.
That's not our world.
Not of this world? I do not understand.
- We got a magic gate.
- How did you get the language we?
- From some prisoners of war.
- Our people? They are still alive?
Why?
- They will be fuel.
- Sacrificing them?
- No.
- That is a crime.
Children Orc...
We do not want war. We just
want to protect our people.
If you help us, I promise
you'll get your baby back.
You have to let a small
team kill kesatriamu.
You're embarrassing your people.
Orc Horde need not weak.
Care about our tradition, war lords.
You know what to do.
- Why do you bother her?
- We fight hard.
- Why are you mengkhanati our people?
- Only I can control you.
Blackhand might make you weak.
Do not mess with death, Gul'dan.
The price is worth it.
You want to hold your son?
- He'll be a leader.
- In contrast to today.
You challenged her.
Gul'dan bring destruction to us.
- Whatever will be.
What is wrong?
I'm curious about Gul'dan.
- What do you want to know?
- You've seen it.
Full of fire and ash.
They're here.
A waitress? I could kill you with ease.
He is my brother. The
king is my husband.
- You are the wife of the leader of the tribe?
- I think so.
- Kill you will bring honor.
- Not among my people.
It's a cold night. I
think you'll need this.
It will make you feel warm.
Another of our village on fire tonight.
The village where I was born.
I can not imagine the
horror that you can carry.
But this need not happen.
It has been many years
there was peace in the land
Peace between different
races from around the world.
What is this?
I can pull it out.
There is life here for you, Garona.
Life with freedom.
That is, if you want it.
He made a gate.
"Darkness came true."
That's pretty awful.
Glad I could see trees
again. And also the snow.
Even from a distance.
Remember when we were
there in the first forest?
There is always a life.
We lost our house when
Gul'dan authorities.
- One Orc can not do that.
- Are you sure?
Look around you. It does
not remind you of anything?
We all need to respect life, my friend.
Gul'dan must be stopped.
We are not strong
enough to defeat Gul'dan.
But with the help of
humans, we can do it.
I want it.
- This is to protect you.
- I do not need anyone to protect me.
See what are you?
You watch first.
- My name is Khadgar.
- Sorry, Khadgar.
I think we've got a bond.
I've released you from prison.
I try to keep ahead.
At least you do not read.
- What is your problem with me?
- What?
- Did you hurt yourself?
- I do not want to lie.
Well done.
Why are you laughing?
You humans could survive without
big muscles to protect you?
- You easily broken bones.
- It's not important to us.
- How can you survive?
- Broken bones heal and become stronger.
Strong man.
- Sorry.
- No need.
My name, Garona, meaning "hard worker."
My mother was burned alive
because of giving birth.
- But they do not kill you.
- As a slave.
They gave us the task
to deliver the Orcs.
My parents gave me the Kerathor
others when I was 6 years old.
Together with my brothers and sisters.
Give children in Kerathor
bring honor to the family.
Give their son floated into town
and trained by the most
powerful wizards in the region.
I had wanted to run.
It was really a fun story.
Large gate.
- Why do they need a lot of prisoners?
- They are wood for the fire.
To keep the gate open.
How much more do they want to bring?
All. They are a group of war.
When the portal is open,
they will keep coming.
Send word to Stormwind.
Garona, we have to go.
Here it is not safe.
- Durotan.
- There is a black stone that touches the sky.
- I want to meet with their leaders.
- What?
I saw you with them.
You know what they do.
And you know what is done
by Gul'dan to my people.
His death.
He must be stopped.
Tell them, Blackrock, as the
sun reaches its highest point.
OK.
Chieftain, when I go
back, can I join your clan?
You're safe here.
- There is trouble everywhere.
- Then do not go anymore.
They are now in urgent need Guardian.
Maybe the boy can help.
- That's the solution.
- Easy for you to say.
- Fort Dwan 'to work overtime.
- Can not.
- We will not supply you anymore.
- Enough!
You all been called to Stormwind before.
If we do not unite to fight
this enemy, we will be destroyed.
- This is your war, not our war.
- Honourable.
Commander.
The orcs built a portal
to carry the team.
If we do not stop them now, we
probably will not get the chance again.
Where is she? Where the
protection of Azeroth?
- Where the Guardian?
- Where is he?
- We pause for a moment.
- Take breaks as long as possible.
We're done.
We've been taking care of what is left.
- The remaining?
- Callan was among them.
Father?
I am fine.
You made me worry.
- Where's the rest of your troops?
- They took all alive.
- Everything.
- Calm down.
You're alive.
I'm a warrior.
He will not ask for a meeting if
he thought could beat Gul'dan alone.
- He must have scared her.
- He can not do anything.
Loca...
Meeting this sudden...
- As a trap.
- Not.
- Can be.
What do you think?
This opportunity is
too good to be ignored.
I guess we have no choice.
We must stop the orcs open portal.
But we will need help.
- What if he's lying?
- Orc do not lie.
- That's dishonorable actions.
Similarly, rather than
betray their own kind?
Durotan protect his
clan. The sell is Gul'dan.
How do you know Durotan?
He was freed and he
is loved by his clan.
- He is a strong leader.
- He won the trust of his clan.
You should join us.
It's a sign.
To protect yourself.
- With this?
- Yes.
Search the Guardian.
What is this?
I've seen it and collect clues.
- Do you copy this file from?
- Guardian.
And this?
And this, this...
I researched...
I am the Guardian. I, not him.
I thought you would want to help.
Do not think. You can help.
I could use you.
If you want to help protect
the king, leave all to me.
- An interesting selection.
- Guardian.
I need your help. I found the book.
There is an illustration
showing on the gate.
We can trace it.
There is a hidden way to get there.
U-turn.
See?
What do you think the Orcs call?
You can find it there.
Guardian burn your research results?
He's just trying to protect you.
Get ready for a surprise attack.
- The spies are already in place.
- Good.
I am the King Llane.
I hear you want to talk.
Ask them when they plan to return?
Our world is destroyed.
There is no home anymore for us.
We are not responsible for
the destruction of your home.
War will not solve anything.
He says for the Orcs,
war solve everything.
And why is he here?
To save my people.
Stopping again spilled more lives.
There is something
that makes them corrupt.
Poison everything with magic.
It all had to be destroyed
so that my people can be safe.
There are people that we capture.
He uses them as a
sacrifice to the portal.
You have to attack our
camp and drove them out.
Otherwise they will die.
Two days.
If we do this, protect them until then.
I've been trying.
Trap!
Orc, protect our camp!
Focus.
Come on!
Look out!
You are okay?
Quickly find the others, quickly!
I'll pick the other.
We'll get out of here.
He will cover our tracks.
This must end.
- Protect him.
- Good.
Formation shield!
No.
Feel.
All.
Kill them all!
Retreat to the castle!
See.
Nice.
Look out!
Medivh!
Son of man.
Shoot.
Medivh!
Where is she?
He's here!
- She's hurt.
- We have to take him.
- I'll take the horse.
- You're not going to get when riding a horse.
Bawa kudaku.
Put him in front of the fireplace.
- No. He's what?
- I've told him not to leave the place.
- We need help, now.
- Go.
There are drugs that should I prepare.
You and this baby had to leave, now.
You're a traitor, Durotan.
No. I appreciate our first who.
- As you used to do.
- It is over.
- Now the situation is different.
- There is still hope.
Our children.
Do not make me take his life.
You're the leader.
Give me advice.
Will you miss people?
See our children.
Now go.
You.
Where is that person?
He told me to take care of you.
- You come.
- You're alive.
Lothar son died.
Because I.
- Lothar will hate me.
- And that makes you sad.
He was a great soldier.
- It is known to people.
- As Orc.
I'm not an Orc.
I'm also not human.
When I was young I never felt it.
I was traveling to distant places.
Searching...
Wisdom, and few relationships
with people who look after.
In my travels, I meet people
who are strong, and honorable.
Among them was a woman who accept me.
Who loved me.
There was a time I lived happily.
If the love that you need...
... You must be willing
to end the world.
- Do you have it?
- No.
I saved this for you.
This...
It's my gift to you.
Come on.
All exchange for dummies.
Strange creatures.
- We also.
- You are mahuk terrible.
We are from the south
already know about you.
Remember that joins us.
You give them a failure.
- All of them.
- Durotan would not agree with all of this.
And why do you care what
she thought was a traitor?
Your son is the leader of the clan.
He's got his own desires.
When you appreciate it.
Now...
Come here.
I will give you strength.
They will poison first.
Then we arrest them, bring them here.
I will stand in front
of them, let them see...
How strong I am now.
As I said, people are practical.
It's a new beginning. Time permitting.
Breathe in the air, just you.
Forgive me.
Nothing.
It has happened.
I long abused his right.
I will not blame you.
I was very young.
Come here.
My entire life...
I've never felt pain like now.
- Street!
- We have to hurry.
Burn them!
Quick!
- I'll be a blood bath with you.
- Maybe, but not now.
Go if you want, I can
not give anything more.
For the good of your children, Draka...
Go on, now.
They should not trust you
as a leader of the orcs.
Fast.
Khadgar, how dare you come here!
- Exit!
- I'm here to seek your wisdom.
- But now there is nothing for you here.
- The guard was ill.
- What?
- He was poisoned by them.
Ridiculous.
- What do you know about the portal of darkness?
- You're back,
- And accuses...
- Where is he?
- Thats it.
- What's that
The shape of the current lack of them.
You think he's just like a guard?
Protects.
No one knows about its existence beyond
the console, and it will stay that way.
And you mention the time
portal near darkness.
- What did he do?
- I do not know, he never melalkukan it before.
- Khadgar.
- I know you, from the library.
You Aloman?
I put the rest of
kekutanku to call here.
- Guards have betrayed us.
- How do you know?
- I see the evil in his eyes.
- He dominated.
If he is not stopped,
the world will burn.
I did not have the
strength to beat the keeper.
The guard is just a name.
Actual guards of this world
are human beings themselves.
I know you see what
they can do and can not.
That's why you left them. Nothing...
Could stand against the darkness.
Alone.
I do not know what you want me to do.
Yes, you know.
Believe in your friends.
Together, you can save this duia.
Always remember...
Light comes from the darkness...
And of darkness...
Come on.
thanks.
You'll be a keeper.
For all you have done.
What happened?
Looks like I've let the
orcs into this world.
The feeling was strange.
I do not even know what I've done.
I just do not remember.
All that I protect, had I...
Destroy.
I can not control this.
No one can.
5 legion to close this road.
10 again here, and
here, on the mountain.
Supplies here. While
the eastern sea here.
If we are in this position, we are
in a state of the most powerful.
- Can not.
- You got a better choice?
Their people more 10 times.
How?
- To be honest it's not easy. - Our
primary goal is not to let them kemari-
If we fail, a matter of
time before they beat us.
What are your suggestions?
Send all that we got.
Destroy them, and end
as soon as possible.
- And Orcs left? - We take care of it
later. - Until they dominate the government?
- Your Highness.
- Medivh, you came.
Yes. I feel...
- Filled back.
- We need you.
We consider our options, some
believe that there is no choice.
- We need advice.
- And I have.
- I've met Durotan.
- You met Durotan.
And Gul'dan gathered strength.
- With their help we can destroy this gate.
- That does not change my plans.
- What plan?
- Anduin believe we have to attack with full force.
I'm afraid it will make the
government had no defense.
How many legions do you
need to defeat the orcs?
5 in this place, in the mountains
10, 10 again to protect the city.
We've lost 18 legion.
- At least 1, 2, 3.
- It can be done.
No, it could not be done.
- With 3 legion, under my power...
- With all due respect,
bus not expected.
- I've made you disappointed?
- Where have you been diving 6 years?
- Please, Anduin. Medivh is a keeper.
- Not as you remember.
He is unstable, and he will not
be there when you really need them.
- Keep your words, Anduin.
- I did it for you.
If I see there is a small chance
to win, but this was a suicide.
It's about Gul'dan?
It was a tragedy.
So far to win approval...
- You did not know.
- He already knows that.
And you let him play as a soldier...
You killed him!
- Calm down.
- Take him to the cells to cool down.
First you do not like this.
I will protect the government.
You want action?
- Why are you here?
- King...
He will fight.
With the release guardian,
Durotan would kill Gul'dan...
- Do not trust him.
- I told you,
- Orc will not lie.
- Not really.
Do not believe Medhiv.
I will try to protect your king.
Do not go with him.
Why?
I do not want you to get hurt.
And come back alive.
Hey, walk everywhere!
Now there is a new enemy.
I thought it was you.
What happened?
I'm sorry, Durotan.
I do not see why we
should join with humans.
Mahluknya itself.
I am wrong.
Gul'dan wanted to destroy us.
Mana Draka? Aman?
Sorry.
Why do you follow it?
In order to see him now like.
I will personally showed them.
No one else I can trust
the safety of my family.
Take care of them while I was away?
Ready.
I will try to do my best.
We'll be fine. I'll take care of here.
Take me to the portal.
Guard.
I know you're just doing your job,
and I'm also good in doing my job.
But now I'm calm. So,
if you open this door...
So I can protect the king.
Open the door! Or I'll...
- Where have you been?
- Long story.
- How much time we have.
- Less than 10 minutes.
Clothes, commander.
Sorry.
They were in front of us.
- I hope we're not too late.
- We can not chase them.
- Rajaku need me.
- There is a need you.
If you want hands to your
king, then stop the demon first.
You coming?
Mana Medivh?
There are demons that we have to kill
You are young Durotan and Draka,
and you will become a leader.
I Duratan.
Gorath child.
The leader of the clan Fastwolf.
And I'm here to membuh Gul'dan.
You're not the leader of the clan.
You're stupid.
There were still alive.
You're going to end them quickly.
I hope you know.
Durotan.
Your clan is weak,
and you are a traitor.
I accept your challenge, and I alone
will lift your heart out of your body.
Wait, you have to be prepared.
It will not be long.
Right here.
He opened the portal,
we have to shut it down.
We did it.
I do not have time for this. Durotan.
Thats it.
You're a disgrace.
Keep fighting.
Listen to him.
Gül'e!
You do not have the honor.
You will follow this demon?
You will do it?
You want to join this demon?
I am not going to.
I follow Orc truth.
A leader.
You want to go?
Would you like to go?
And you will feel it.
You will receive strength, and
you will be stronger than any Orc.
With this power, you
will destroy Medhiv.
Look at you.
Now admit my new world.
Shit.
We are now alone.
With you.
To prison, we will free our people!
Attack!
- Nak.
- He...
Good, now try to beat him.
Kauakan tahu.
It went well?
He opened, do something.
Well, I overcome this.
You Medhiv governance.
Over here!
What?
You want to fight me?
Advanced!
Shoot!
You're not Orcs.
Look out!
Come, my lord. Let them
feel the power of orcs.
Where is she?
Find them.
Hey, wake up!
- You...
- You okay?
- Good. I thank you.
- Yes.
We must have a plan.
- What now?
- Guard alone should talk to him.
Hold on. You want me to try?
I get to him. Distract.
- And what?
- Bring Medhiv to that place.
That is all?
Medhiv.
There is something.
Back at us.
Medhiv.
Kill me.
Moreover, I have no
reason to live anymore.
After all it's just a
game to you, is not it?
We believe in you.
Do not kill your king.
Do not kill your friends.
Whatever your plans... cancel.
You challenge me?
Now.
Now!
- Portalnya close!
- No!
You're stronger than him.
Light comes from the darkness.
And of darkness...
Come to light!
A.
I have to go.
I am proud of you.
Quickly, through the portal, stop him!
Be prepared.
- Forward!
- Quickly, through the portal!
Advanced!
Follow me!
Create a boundary line.
You into prison.
- And saved them.
- Quick!
- Fast!
- I'll hold them.
Quick to the portal.
- Fast.
- Come on.
Over there! Help me push!
Fast, push!
- Fast!
- Take care.
We release our people
as much as possible!
It was like this. Weak.
Can not do anything.
Forgive me.
I have to save us all.
I understand.
Quick!
We are losing guard.
I have come to ask for respect for kill.
Do it.
There is no point, is not it?
Look around, we are surrounded.
By killing me, it's the
only hope we're reconciled.
You told me to kill you
would be able to honor.
With kill me, you'll be a hero.
Last.
Bring peace between the orcs and humans.
You must.
No!
Leader.
I support you.
Orc.
Kill him.
Kill him!
Wait! Our sacred covenant!
But who won? Tell me.
- We have to respect our traditions.
- I will not obey you.
APB are you waiting for?
Make perintaku!
Traitor!
Move over, I'll do it myself.
Who will obey? Who else?
If you do this, you'll start a war.
And the war was just beginning.
Through your son...
I will teach her.
Who is the owner of this knife?
- I take it from the king's neck.
- There must be an explanation.
Yes. He has made his decision.
I can not believe.
Maybe you and I do not know him as king.
There is no bigger than this lesson.
Of a king...
Sacrificing himself for his people.
But the sacrifices that
need to be secured...
We should proceed.
If we show our unity to grieve
the kind people who die...
His death will not be in vain.
To Azeroth!